freewebarcade.com 2018-12-26

# Free Web Arcade - Privacy Policy

FreeWebArcade.Com is deeply committed to your privacy. The following outlines our continued support of protecting our users' privacy.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Personal information that you provide to our site will not be disclosed to any third-party sites.

**COOKIES**  
We use cookies to passively collect demographic information, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISEMENT**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**EXTERNAL LINKS**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. e encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**CONTACT US**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement, don't hesitate to [contact us](http://www.freewebarcade.com/contact.php).
